etradeasia.com 2019-07-31

# TradeAsia / Global B2B - Privacy & Cookie Policy

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the e-TradeAsia.com Site. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and e-TradeAsia.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept. 

**The Information We Collect**

Registration Information: At the time you register to become a Member of the Site, you will be asked to complete an application form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business ("Registration Information.") 

Publishing Information: If you upload or submit any information to e-TradeAsia.com to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Listing, Trade Leads, News Listing, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information ("Publishing Information"). 

**How We May Use Information**

General: We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message. 

Registration Information: We may use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which e-TradeAsia.com determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

Publishing Information: All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to e-TradeAsia.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us. 

Top

**Disclosure of Information**

We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of e-TradeAsia.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. 

If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of Service Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to TradeAsia or others. 

Top

**Minors**

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information. 

Top

**Security Measures**

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. 

As a Member, your Registration Information and Publishing Information can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., Member ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. 

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

Top

**Cookies**

_What are cookies?_

Cookies is a small data of text files that the web browser stores on your hard drive. Cookies collect and store certain information which can be accessed by web servers. In addition, most major websites use cookies. Because cookies are necessary to facilitate browsing and to make it more user-friendly, and they do not damage your computer. Some cookies are extremely useful because they can improve your user experience when you return to a website you have already visited. Cookies will remember your preferences, will know how you use the website, and will adapt the content you are shown so that it is more relevant to your personal interests and needs. 

**Use Cookies of on TradeAsia**

TradeAsia may uses “cookies”. Cookies tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, help us measure the effectiveness of ads and web searches, and give us insights into user behavior so we can improve our communications and products. In addition, Cookies on this website that do not require your approval. 

Cookies help us to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Also, we use cookies which are necessary to make navigating and visiting web sites user friendly. Moreover, cookies tell us which parts of our websites visitors have visited, help us measure the effectiveness of ads and web searches, and give us insights into user behavior so we can improve our services. 

**Categories of Cookies**

● Strictly Necessary Cookies 

These cookies are essential to enable you to browse around our websites and use their features. 

● Performance Cookies 

These cookies collect information about how you use our websites. For example, which pages visitors go often. This data may be used to help optimize our websites and make them easier for you to navigate. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. 

● Functionality Cookies 

These cookies allow our websites to remember choices you make while browsing - for instance, user names, languages choices, and your location that you have already been entered. They may also be used to keep track of what featured products or videos have been viewed to avoid repetition. Also, these cookies collect anonymous information and cannot track your movements on other websites. 

● Marketing Cookies 

These cookies enable us and our carefully selected retail partners to deliver advertisements to you which match your interests by, for example, collecting information about products you have browsed or ordered on our website. In addition, they remember whether you have visited a website or not, and this information can be shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Cookies for improving group targeting and advertising will often be linked to site functionality provided by other organizations. 

**Web Beacons**

Some pages on our website may contain images known as "web beacons", some of which may be served by third parties. Beacons can be embedded in online content, videos, and emails, and can allow a server to read certain types of information from your device, know when you have viewed particular content or a particular email message, determine the time and date on which you viewed the beacon, and the IP address of your device. We and certain third parties use beacons for a variety of purposes, including to analyze the use of our Services and (in conjunction with cookies) to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you. 

**How do I disable and prevent the use of Cookies?**

You may restrict, block or delete the Cookies from this website at any time by changing the configuration of your browser following the steps indicated below. While settings are different in each browser, Cookies are normally configured in the "Preferences" or "Tools" menu. For further details on configuring Cookies in your browser, see the "Help" menu in the browser itself. 

Please note, you can completely disable cookies in your browser at any time. It is important to note that if you change your settings and block certain cookies, you will not be able to take full advantage of some of the features of this site, and we may not be able to provide some of the features you previously chose to use. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact e-TradeAsia.com in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that e-TradeAsia.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in e-TradeAsia.com's possession. This Privacy Policy was last amended on June 6, 2006. 

Top

**Correcting Your Information**

You can access, view and edit your Member Information and Publishing Information through your Account with e-TradeAsia.com. To update or correct such information, please click here.
